[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 29, "question": "Why you seem quite happy with it afterwards, why you then felt the need to tweet quite hostile tweets in my direction which then sparked this furor amongst the transgender community because I feel pretty peeved about it?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "you", "seem", "quite", "happy", "with", "it", "afterwards", ",", "why", "you", "then", "felt", "the", "need", "to", "tweet", "quite", "hostile", "tweets", "in", "my", "direction", "which", "then", "sparked", "this", "furor", "amongst", "the", "transgender", "community", "because", "I", "feel", "pretty", "peeved", "about", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 30, "answer": "Well, I'm sorry that you feel offended.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "sorry", "that", "you", "feel", "offended", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "NN", "CC", "RB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "WP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 43, "question": "What did I do wrong?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "I", "do", "wrong", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 44, "answer": "You called -- so before commercial break, we had a lovely conversation and then all of a sudden you said, who was formerly a man.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "called", "--", "so", "before", "commercial", "break", ",", "we", "had", "a", "lovely", "conversation", "and", "then", "all", "of", "a", "sudden", "you", "said", ",", "who", "was", "formerly", "a", "man", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 49, "question": "Why you didn't correct me?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "you", "did", "n't", "correct", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 50, "answer": "I did not because I was scared.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "not", "because", "I", "was", "scared", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 51, "question": "Did you feel that strongly?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "feel", "that", "strongly", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 52, "answer": "OCK: I did not because ...", "answer_tokens": ["OCK", ":", "I", "did", "not", "because", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 53, "question": "Scared of what?", "question_tokens": ["Scared", "of", "what", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 54, "answer": "... I was fair and I want it to be a cordial guess ...", "answer_tokens": ["...", "I", "was", "fair", "and", "I", "want", "it", "to", "be", "a", "cordial", "guess", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 55, "question": "Scared of what?", "question_tokens": ["Scared", "of", "what", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 56, "answer": "... and I think that that was probably incorrect of me.", "answer_tokens": ["...", "and", "I", "think", "that", "that", "was", "probably", "incorrect", "of", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 166, "question": "To become a real woman as you say in the book, why is it offensive?", "question_tokens": ["To", "become", "a", "real", "woman", "as", "you", "say", "in", "the", "book", ",", "why", "is", "it", "offensive", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 167, "answer": "I think that we need to have a discussion about what gender is.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "we", "need", "to", "have", "a", "discussion", "about", "what", "gender", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 205, "question": "OK, can I ask mine first then you can ask yours?", "question_tokens": ["OK", ",", "can", "I", "ask", "mine", "first", "then", "you", "can", "ask", "yours", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "JJ", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 206, "answer": "OK.", "answer_tokens": ["OK", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 287, "question": "What did you make of the second interview, the general debate about what I've had with Janet Mock?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "make", "of", "the", "second", "interview", ",", "the", "general", "debate", "about", "what", "I", "'ve", "had", "with", "Janet", "Mock", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 288, "answer": "You know, I watched her from the green room.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "watched", "her", "from", "the", "green", "room", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Janet Mock"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 438, "question": "And if you sit down with your American pie charts of culture diversity in the country and divide up your humor quote \"up in the show\" in a very specific kind of scientific PC (ph) pleasing way, I got his point that in the end, you're drifting away from what humor should be which is just spontaneous funny stuff because it really matter, does it?", "question_tokens": ["And", "if", "you", "sit", "down", "with", "your", "American", "pie", "charts", "of", "culture", "diversity", "in", "the", "country", "and", "divide", "up", "your", "humor", "quote", "``", "up", "in", "the", "show", "''", "in", "a", "very", "specific", "kind", "of", "scientific", "PC", "(", "ph", ")", "pleasing", "way", ",", "I", "got", "his", "point", "that", "in", "the", "end", ",", "you", "'re", "drifting", "away", "from", "what", "humor", "should", "be", "which", "is", "just", "spontaneous", "funny", "stuff", "because", "it", "really", "matter", ",", "does", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VB", "RP", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "``", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "''", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ":", "NN", ":", "VBG", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "WP", "NN", "MD", "VB", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "JJR", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 439, "answer": "All right.", "answer_tokens": ["All", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 495, "question": "And what do we make of this Ben Ferguson?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "do", "we", "make", "of", "this", "Ben", "Ferguson", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 496, "answer": "Well, I think two three things.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "two", "three", "things", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ben Ferguson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 511, "question": "I think it's sad that we still hail woody Allen in the midst of all these mess?", "question_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "sad", "that", "we", "still", "hail", "woody", "Allen", "in", "the", "midst", "of", "all", "these", "mess", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 512, "answer": "I agree.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "agree", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Allen"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 535, "question": "So a pretty serious warning tonight about the threat from toothpastes and cosmetic tubes, generally, of flights to Russia during the Sochi games, what do you make of the threat that was revealed?", "question_tokens": ["So", "a", "pretty", "serious", "warning", "tonight", "about", "the", "threat", "from", "toothpastes", "and", "cosmetic", "tubes", ",", "generally", ",", "of", "flights", "to", "Russia", "during", "the", "Sochi", "games", ",", "what", "do", "you", "make", "of", "the", "threat", "that", "was", "revealed", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 536, "answer": "Well, I think it's part of the general feeling about this Olympics that the Russians have probably done a good job of protecting the inside of the Olympics, you know, within the Olympic compound.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "part", "of", "the", "general", "feeling", "about", "this", "Olympics", "that", "the", "Russians", "have", "probably", "done", "a", "good", "job", "of", "protecting", "the", "inside", "of", "the", "Olympics", ",", "you", "know", ",", "within", "the", "Olympic", "compound", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Russia", "Sochi"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Peter"]}, "docId": "140205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 549, "question": "Would you feel comfortable going there now as a visitor?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "feel", "comfortable", "going", "there", "now", "as", "a", "visitor", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 550, "answer": "First of all, I think Peter's right.", "answer_tokens": ["First", "of", "all", ",", "I", "think", "Peter", "'s", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1970"], "ORGANIZATION": ["Narcotics Division"], "LOCATION": ["U.S."]}, "docId": "140205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "NN", ",", "NN", "NN", ",", "NN", "NN", "NN", "DT", "CD", "POS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 600, "question": "... heroine use is on the rise?", "question_tokens": ["...", "heroine", "use", "is", "on", "the", "rise", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 601, "answer": "I go back dealing with drug, drug crime, drug rehabilitation 'till the 1970's when I was head of the Narcotics Division in the U.S. Attorney's Office when I was like 26 years old.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "go", "back", "dealing", "with", "drug", ",", "drug", "crime", ",", "drug", "rehabilitation", "'till", "the", "1970", "'s", "when", "I", "was", "head", "of", "the", "Narcotics", "Division", "in", "the", "U.S.", "Attorney", "'s", "Office", "when", "I", "was", "like", "26", "years", "old", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "RBR", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 639, "question": "Has the reality been better or worst than you feared or expected?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "the", "reality", "been", "better", "or", "worst", "than", "you", "feared", "or", "expected", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "RBR", "CC", "JJS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 640, "answer": "It's been much better than I ever imagined it could be.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "been", "much", "better", "than", "I", "ever", "imagined", "it", "could", "be", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 679, "question": "Want to elaborate on his jerkiness?", "question_tokens": ["Want", "to", "elaborate", "on", "his", "jerkiness", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 680, "answer": "Sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]